Dilshod Ramatilloev

(998)936604530 | iamdilshodboy@gmail.com | Tashkent, Tashkent

Summary

I possess a diverse professional background in software development, with expertise in frontend development, web application maintenance, and agile methodology. I have experience in managing teams, planning sprints, conducting meetings, and assisting other developers. My skills in design patterns, architectural solutions, testing, debugging, and refactoring have contributed to successful projects, including CRM systems, POS systems, ecommerce platforms, and landing pages. My commitment to excellence and problem-solving abilities make me a valuable asset in the industry.

Experience

Invan LLC | Tashkent, Tashkent Lead Front End Developer | 09/2022 - 03/2023

Responsibilities:

- · Conduct daily stand-ups, retrospective meetings
- · Plan sprints and monitoring the project progress
- · Help other frontend developers to code and conduct code reviews

Accomplishments:

- Applied various design patterns and architectural solutions to the client side of the POS system
- Managed a team of 12 developers under Agile methodology using tools like Jira and Slack

EPAM Systems | Tashkent, Tashkent Software Engineer | 06/2022 - 09/2022

Responsibilities:

- Internal web application maintenance
- Implement new features
- · Test, debug, and refactor existing code
- · Provide optimizations where necessary

Udevs | Tashkent, Tashkent Front End Developer | 10/2020 - 06/2022

Responsibilities:

- · Write code to solve business problems
- Work in a team of developers to deliver value in weekly sprints
- Participate in code reviews, trainings, daily stand-ups
- Troubleshoot and debug the client side of web applications
- · Apply unit tests to existing functionality
- · Integrate frontend to the server using REST API

Accomplishments:

• Participated in around 10 projects of different difficulty and type such as CRM systems, POS systems, ecommerce platforms, and landing pages (6 projects are actively developed and finished)

Skills

Javascript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Next.js, GraphQL, REST, Functional Programming, Object Oriented Programming, Design Patterns, Data Structures and Algorithms, GIT, Sass (Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets), CSS, Agile, JIRA, Jest

Education

Westminster International University in Tashkent | Tashkent, Tashkent Business Information Systems | 05/2023

 Learned how to translate business needs into technical problems and built fully functional SaaS product for a startup company as the final project

•	Gained knowledge and experience in many fields of software development such as desktop applications development, mobile development, game development, web development, machine learning and data science